BGM
Hello everyone, I'm Yuri Kuboshi.
Today I'm here just to eat Machuuka, which I've always been curious about.
Gyoza.
I've always wanted to go.
It's the first time I've been here.
This one's really nice.
This is Momotaro.
Momotaro!
I've wanted to come here for a long time.
Wow, it's so crowded and popular!
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Excuse me.
That's great.
Good, good.
Excuse me.
Good.
Thank you very much.
Sorry, sir. Yes, you can. One fried wonton, then,
What shall we do?
What would you recommend?
Stir-fried vegetables.
Okay, one stir-fried vegetable.
That's all for now.
Please.
Menu.
Mmm.
I wanted to eat the "I'm sorry, I'm sorry".
I'm sorry, I thought you had a party in there.
I don't know, it's boring.
It's got vinegar.
Soy sauce.
Soy sauce. Soy sauce with vinegar.
It smelled so good from the outside.
You don't get that very often.
Members' purchases.
What?
If I say it wrong, you'll see me not borrowing.
If I say it wrong, you'll see me not being enthusiastic.
I didn't do anything today.
This is Member Morise.
Is this okay? Thank you very much.
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit!
Your mother is too nice.
Stir-fried vegetables.
Rice.
With soup.
Delicious.
I want to eat it while it's over there.
Let's eat first.
Thank you very much.
It's very hot, very hot, be careful, it's me, it's different today, thank you very much.
I'll be careful.
It's a mixed bag today.
It's a varied day.
It's a mixed day.
I like beautiful women.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I found out while I was dipping into this curry that I'd ordered a lot.
I'm too happy.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. Is this okay? Okay? No problem... I can't give you any...
She...
먹자
와,야... 와, 야... Bon appétit.
Looks delicious.
The sticky, crunchy kind.
Bon appétit, delicious.
Delicious.
Crunchy.
It feels even better now.
Hot.
Hot. 뜨거워.
It's a bit tasty.
Bon appétit.
Mmm.
It's delicious.
I don't like it when you say it like that.
For moments like this.
I'm going to work hard. Can you do it? 이곳은 매우 유명한 곳입니다. 매우 유명한 곳입니다. 매우 유명한 곳입니다.
매우 유명한 곳입니다.
매우 유명한 곳입니다. Delicious
Delicious
Delicious.
Delicious. 아이고, 아이고. Good, good, good. Good, good, good.
It's delicious.
I'm going.
I'm going. I'm going to do a very creepy room. I'm so excited. I'm so excited.
It's too much.
Too much? It's okay, it's okay.
This is Kubo style.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Everyone's doing all kinds of cute stuff during the stream.
Are you okay?
Cosplay?
It's so cute.
Too long? You know what?
Is this your style?
Thank you for the food.
It's delicious.
Thank you very much for the food. Thank you very much for the food.
I'll be back.
Thank you very much.
That was great.
Oh, man.
Oh, my God.
It's still light.
I'm so happy.
Wishing you all the best in Chirizuka!
That was Momotaro-san, the first one.
Bye-bye, bye-bye.